{
    "subject": "resource/American_Association_for_Respiratory_Care",
    "predicate": "ontology/locationCity",
    "object": "resource/Irving,_Texas",
    "human_readable": "The American Association for Respiratory Care is located in Irving, Texas.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.970321536064148,
            "question": "Is the American Association for Respiratory Care located in Texas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8997330665588379,
            "question": "Where is the American Association for Respiratory Care located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8185282349586487,
            "question": "What is the location of the American Association for Respiratory Care?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7185097336769104,
            "question": "What is the address of the American Association for Respiratory Care?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7153575420379639,
            "question": "In what state is the American Association for Respiratory Care headquartered?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6871187686920166,
            "question": "What organization's headquarters are in Irving, Texas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6220712065696716,
            "question": "Where can you find the offices of the American Association for Respiratory Care?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6087769865989685,
            "question": "Which city serves as the base of operations for the American Association for Respiratory Care?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5998969078063965,
            "question": "What city is home to the American Association for Respiratory Care?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5438838005065918,
            "question": "If you wanted to visit the American Association for Respiratory Care, where would you go?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The American Association for Respiratory Care is located in Irving, Texas.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7404_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What city is home to the American Association for Respiratory Care?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7404_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which city serves as the base of operations for the American Association for Respiratory Care?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7404_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where can you find the offices of the American Association for Respiratory Care?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7404_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7404_117.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7404_123.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7404_126.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7404_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7404_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7404_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7404_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7404_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7404_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7404_92.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that the American Association for Respiratory Care (AARC) is located at 9425 N MacArthur Blvd #100, Irving, TX 75063. This confirms that it is indeed located in Irving, Texas."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}